Aaron Summers here with tight end Noah
F, now a New Orleans Saint. It took us a
couple times to get you. You were here
last year. Why was this the right fit
for you now?
>> Yeah, I think it was just a good fit um
coming in and being a part of this this
team. I think there's a lot of young
talent, so I'm excited to be here and uh
be able to contribute.
>> Head coach Kellen Moore said that they
really liked you and they went through
the process last year. What does that
tell you about how much they value you
and and want you here? Yeah, I think
that definitely said a lot um to come
back again and and revisit that and uh
be able to get a deal done um which is
really cool. So, um it's it's nice that
they, you know, have that want for me
and have that faith in me. So, um I'm
looking forward to giving it everything
I got to to prove them right.
>> What do you like about Coach Moore's
scheme?
>> Uh I like everything about it. It's very
tight end friendly. Um he loves the
tight ends. He loves to use them. Um
obviously Joan's already here. I got to
I've gotten to know him over the years
pretty well and I'm excited to work with
him and uh um just get after it. So,
it's going to be fun.
>> How will your skill set complement what
Jawan Johnson brings and and how they
use the tight ends?
>> Yeah, I think I think we both offer a
good receiving skill set. Um he's done a
great job of, you know, making a name
for himself and um has has had some good
really good production and um I think I
can offer some of that also and uh be a
good be a good one-two punch with him
and and uh try and try and make defenses
fear us. So, I'm excited about that and
uh to be able to contribute in that in
that standpoint.
>> What are you looking forward to about
joining the Saints culture and this fan
base because they are very passionate.
>> Yeah. No, I'm I'm definitely super
excited. I I've come to see just being
here in a short time that everybody
loves their Saints and uh um I'm excited
for the fans. I'm excited for the food
and and the culture and all that and all
those things. So, I haven't spent much
time in the South before, but I'm
excited to be here and I'm going to
fully embrace that. What are you looking
forward to most about being in the
Superdome and having that be your home
field?
>> Yeah, honestly, I've played there once
before when I was in Seattle and uh it's
one it's been one of my favorite places
to play. It's such a cool environment.
Um being in a dome, all the lights, all
the all those things. And it's really
cool cuz I get to be in a Saints uniform
now, which is uh some of the coolest
uniforms in the NFL. Um some of the
greatest colors also black and gold is
pretty awesome. So, I'm excited about
that.
>> What are Saints fans going to see from
you on Sundays when you take the field?
uh they're just going to see, you know,
a passionate and uh explosive player
that's excited to be on the field. Um
you know, I'm looking forward to just
giving it everything I got and uh and
being the player that everybody wants me
to be and uh looking forward to making
plays on the field for him.
>> Okay. Off the field,
>> what kind of guy are we getting?
>> Uh I'm a fun, goofy, loving guy. Um
looking forward to being a part of the
community and and embracing the
community and and doing all those things
to to really show love to the people
that support us. So, um, yeah, I try to
I try to exemplify that a lot, though.
>> All right. Very soon we're going to be
starting the season. What would a
successful first year here with the
Saints look like for you?
>> Yeah, I think just contributing any way
they need me to. Um, doing what's asked
of me and and uh trying to, you know,
really really put some good numbers up
and and and help the offense in the in
the right direction that they've already
been in. Um, and and just be another
option for them. So, uh, I'm excited for
that. Hey, we're building right here and
we're happy to have you along with us
and looking forward to this upcoming
season. Welcome.
>> Thank you.